Contact Info

Email

rami.obaid@yh.nackademin.se

Phone

+46 73 748 17 95

GitHub

https://github.com/RamiObaid92/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ramiobaid-102594338

Website

www.ramiobaid.com

Skills

Programming Languages:

C#, JavaScript/TypeScript, C++, Python

Frameworks:

.NET, ASP.NET, React, Angular, MVC

Database Management:

SQL Server, NoSQL, PostgreSQL

Tools & Platforms:

Git, Jira, Unit Tests, VS Code, Visual Studio, Postman

Cloud & DevOps:

Azure Services, Docker, GitHub Actions

Languages

Swedish (Fluent)

English (Fluent)

Rami Obaid

Student / Software Developer

I am goal-oriented and dedicated .NET developer in training with a strong interest in system development and modern web technologies. Experienced in C#, ASP.NET, React, Angular, and SQL Server, with an understanding of the entire development process. I enjoy collaborating in environments where knowledge sharing and problem-solving are key, while also taking ownership and responsibility for my tasks.

My goal is to grow as a developer within an organization where I can contribute to both technical solutions and a positive team culture.

Education

2024 - present .NET Software Development

Nackademin Higher Vocational Education, Stockholm, Sweden

^{2008 - 2011} Electrical-Programme

ST Eriks Upper secondary school, Stockholm, Sweden

Additional Courses

2022 Computer Technology & Computer Networking

Work History

^{2019 - 2020} Delivery Assistant

Family-Owned Import and Wholesale Business, Sydney, Australia

 Imported and delivered tobacco products to retail stores and companies.

^{2016 - 2018} Store Assistant

COOP, Stockholm, Sweden

• Customer service, cashier operations, and product restocking.

^{2016 - 2016} Store Assistant

Shell, Stockholm, Sweden

Customer service, cashier operations, and product restocking.

^{2011 - 2012} Electrician

Gullikssons El, Stockholm, Sweden

• Electrical installations, troubleshooting, and repairs in residential and commercial buildings.